Francis Biddle Collection of International Military Tribunal Nuremberg Trial Documents and Related Material
Francis Biddle Collection of International Military Tribunal Nuremberg Trial Documents and Related Material
1928-1960
1945-1946
Biddle, Francis, 1886-1968.
12 linear ft.
Biddle (1886-1968) was U.S. Attorney General under Franklin D. Roosevelt, and a member of the International Military Tribunal at Nuremberg. Personal papers including correspondence, a journal and notes for Biddle's autobiography, a photograph album and 5 scrapbooks. Bulk of collection consists of trial documents: notes and minutes, indictments, 11 volumes of evidence notes, defense documents, about 50 volumes of trial proceedings, memoranda, appeals, and material on Katyn Forest Massacre. Also includes published material on aspects of international law as related to the trial.
148850
Biographical History
Francis Biddle, lawyer, Attorney General of the United States under President Franklin D. Roosevelt, and member of the International Military Tribunal at Nuremberg, was born in Paris, France, on May 9, 1886, the son of Algernon Sydney and Frances (Robinson) Biddle, and was brought to America in infancy. He attended Haverford School from 1895 to 1899 and Groton School from 1899 to 1905. From Harvard College he received his B.A. cum laude in 1909.
After receiving his LL.B. cum laude from the Harvard Law School in 1911, Mr. Biddle served as private secretary to Supreme Court Justice Oliver Wendell Holmes from 1911 to 1912. He practiced law in Philadelphia, first with Biddle, Paul and Jayne, 1912-1915, and then with Barnes, Biddle and Myers, 1917-1939. Mr. Biddle was appointed special assistant to the United States Attorney for the Eastern District of Pennsylvania, 1922-1926, first chairman of the National Labor Relations Board, 1934, and chief counsel of the joint Congressional committee to investigate the Tennessee Valley Authority, 1938-1939. He was judge for the United States Circuit Court of Appeals, 3d Circuit, 1939-1940, Solicitor General of the United States, 1940-1941, and Attorney General from September 1941 to June 1945. He was appointed United States member of the International Military Tribunal in Nuremberg, to which service most of the papers in this collection refer. Mr. Biddle was also a member of the Permanent Court of Arbitration.
Among his writings are The Llanfear Pattern, a novel, 1927; Mr. Justice Holmes, 1942; Democratic Thinking and the War, 1944; The World's Best Hope, 1949; The Fear of Freedom, 1951; Justice Holmes, Natural Law and the Supreme Court, 1961; the memoirs A Casual Past, 1961, and In Brief Authority, 1962; and contributions to a number of legal publications. Mr. Biddle died at his home on Cape Cod on October 4, 1968.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Francis Biddle Collection of International Military Tribunal Nuremberg Trial Documents and Related Material is divided into four series: Personal papers, Trial documents, Miscellaneous documents and Additions.
Personal papers consist of incoming and outgoing correspondence, 1945-1953, arranged chronologically; a journal, "Notes on Conference," in which Mr. Biddle described the preparations for the trial; a pictorial album of Nuremberg autographed by all the judges at the Trial; and five large scrapbooks. Originals of certain letters and the journal, photocopied for preservation, have been placed at the end of the collection and use has been restricted. The scrapbooks contain a wide variety of items: correspondence, postcards, souvenir items, clippings, photographs and more.
Trial documents, 1945-1946, include material relative to the organization and proceedings of the trial of the major war criminals before the International Military Tribunal at Nuremberg, Germany. There are two sets of papers for the organizational meetings which have been interfiled chronologically. One set, herein called notes, contains verbatim records of the proceedings. The second set, herein called minutes, contains a summary of the proceedings. From October 9, 1945 through November 15, 1945, there are often two sets of papers for each date, i.e., both notes and minutes. Thereafter, from November 16, 1945 through August 30, 1946, only minutes are available. Supporting material was maintained in Mr. Biddle's original order within the organizational meetings. "Notes on Evidence" is a ten-volume bound typescript summary of evidence heard each day at the trial with personal comments on the proceedings by Biddle. The Trial of Major War Criminals before the International Military Tribunal at Nuremberg, published under the Allied Control Authority for Germany (42 vols., Nuremberg, 1946-1949) is the official printed text in English of the proceedings of the trial. Also included are the following documents: a typescript copy of the "Rulings of the Tribunal," with an index whose page references indicate the item numbers of the rulings; memoranda to members of the International Military Tribunal; "Drafts of Judgement" and notes on judgement containing discussions by the judges on the judgement of defendants and for organizations considered criminal. There are also other documents relating to the trial, including some published material consisting of books, articles, and papers arranged alphabetically by author or title.
Bound volumes of trial documents have been assigned numbers for easier identification. A summary of all 69 volumes in the collection is as follows. For more detailed descriptions, including dates of coverage, refer to the Inventory section below.
Volume 1 - Nuremberg (Box 1)
Volumes 2-8 - Notes of Evidence Vol. I-VII (Boxes 3-5)
Volume 9 - Notes of Evidence: Organizations (Box 5)
Volume 10 - Notes of Evidence: Defendants (Box 5)
Volume 11 - Notes of Evidence: Summaries (Box 6)
Volume 12 - Trial of the Major War Criminals, Vol. I: Official Documents (Box 6)
Volumes 13-33 - Trial of the Major War Criminals, Vol. II-XXII: Proceedings (Boxes 6-9)
Volumes 34-35 - Trial of the Major War Criminals, Vol. XXIII and XXIV: Indexes and errata (Box 10)
Volumes 36-53 - Trial of the Major War Criminals, Vol. XXV-XLII: Documents in Evidence (Boxes 10-14)
Volume 54 - Dokumenty Obvineniia po delu, No. 1 [Documents of Indictment, part 1] (Box 15)
Volume 55 - Lager Osventsim [Camp of the Conquered] (Box 15)
Volumes 56-62 - Katyn Forest Massacre (Box 15)
Volume 63 - The Charter and Judgment of the Nurnberg Tribunal Memorandum (Box 16)
Volume 64 - Descheemaeker, Jaques. Le Tribunal Militaire International des Grandes Criminels de Guerre (Box 16)
Volume 65 - Pella, Vespasian V. La Guerre-Crime et les Criminels de Guerre (Box 16)
Volumes 66-67 - Le Proces de Nuremberg, two volumes:: L'Accusation Francaise and Le Proces de Nuremberg: Exposes Introductifs (Box 16)
Volume 68 - Taylor, Telford. Final Report to the Secretary of the Army on the Nuernberg War Crimes Trials under Control Council Law No. 10 (Box 16)
Volume 69 - Vabres, H. Donnedieu de. Le Proces de Nuremberg devant les principes modernes du droit penal international (Box 16)
Miscellaneous documents include published material dealing mainly with aspects of international law as it relates to the trial, arranged alphabetically by author or title.
Additions contains later additions to the collection, including correspondence between Biddle and his wife, spiral notebooks containing Biddle's handwritten notes for his autobiography and a folder of photographs of the trials.
Arrangement of the Collection
See Scope and Content above for a description of how materials are arranged.
Subject and Genre Headings
Historians; Military history; Politics, government and public administration; Biddle, Francis, 1886-1968.; Birkett, Norman Birkett, Baron, 1883-1962.; Donnedieu de Vabres, H. (Henri), 1880-1952.; Pella, Vespasien V., 1897-1952.; Rowe, James H. (James Henry), 1909-1984.; Schacht, Hjalmar Horace Greeley, 1877-1970.; Taylor, Telford.; Wechsler, Herbert, 1909-2000.; Wright, Quincy, 1890-1970.; International Military Tribunal.; World War, 1939-1945 -- Atrocities.; Katyn Massacre, Katynʹ, Russia, 1940.; Nuremberg Trial of Major German War Criminals, Nuremberg, Germany, 1945-1946.; War crime trials -- Germany (West) -- Nuremburg.; Correspondence.; Diaries.; Legal files.; Memorandums.; Photographs.; Lawyers.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Francis Biddle, June 1965 and the Estate of Katherine Chapin Biddle, 1979.
Inventory
- Personal papers
  - Correspondence, 1945-1953 (Box 1)
    See also Additions: Personal papers: Correspondence (Box 19)
  - Notebooks, spiral notebooks, numbered on front covers, containing Biddle's handwritten notes for his autobiography; 11 volumes in 2 folders (Box 20)
    See also Additions: Personal papers: "The Nürnberg Trial" (Box 19)
  - Notes on Conference, October 2-November 17, 1945; photocopy of revised typescript, 45 p. (Box 1)
  - Nuremberg, by Charles W. Alexander, 1946; autographed album, illustrated, 50p. (Box 1)
  - Photographs, 1945-1946; photographs of trial, attorneys, defendants, building and grounds; most are official Army photographs, stamped and identified on the reverse, but a few appear to be personal photographs (Box 20)
  - Scrapbooks
    - Nurnberg I 1945 (Oversize 1)
    - Nurnberg II (Oversize 2)
    - Nurnberg III (Oversize 3)
    - Nurnberg IV (Oversize 4)
    - Nurnberg V (Oversize 5)
- Trial documents
  - London Agreement
    - (London) Agreement...Prosecution and Punishment of the Major War Criminals of the European Axis London, 8th August, 1945; Miscellaneous No. 10, published material 9p.; 2 autographed copies (Box 1)
  - Indictment
    - (London) Indictment presented to the International Military Tribunal ... at Berlin, on the 18th of October 1945; published material, 50 p.; 2 autographed copies (Box 1)
    - International Military Tribunal Indictment No. 1. Societe Egyptienne de Droit International. Brochure No. 1, November, 1945; published material, 70 p., autographed copy (Box 1)
    - International Military Tribunal No. 1, undated; published material 43 p. (Box 1)
    - Rules Relating to Court Procedure, undated; published material rev., 2 p. (Box 1)
  - International Military Tribunal
    - Organizational meetings
      - Notes and minutes
        - October 9, 1945, Notes, 5:00 P.M., typescript, 4 p.; Minutes, 5:00 P.M., typescript copy, 5p. (Box 1)
        - October 10, 1945, Notes, 11:00 A.M., typescript, 9 p.; Minutes, 11:00 A.M., typescript copy, 3 p.; Notes, 2:00 P.M., typescript, 20 p. (Box 1)
        - October 11, 1945, Notes, 10:30 A.M., typescript, 12 p.; Minutes (morning meeting) typescript copy, 1 p.; Notes, 2:00 P.M., typescript, 7 p. (Box 1)
        - October 12, 1945, Notes, 10:30 A.M., typescript, 13 p.; Notes, 3:00 P.M., typescript, 30 p.; Minutes, 3:00 P.M., typescript copy, printed material, 5 p. (Box 1)
        - October 13, 1945, Notes, 10:30 A.M., typescript, 16 p.; Minutes, 10:30 A.M., typescript copy, 2 p.; Notes, 2:15 P.M., typescript, 11 p.; Minutes, 2:15 P.M., typescript copy, 1 p. (Box 1)
        - October 14, 1945, Notes, 3:00 P.M., typescript, 38 p.; Minutes, 3:00 P.M., typescript copy, 2 p. (Box 1)
        - October 15, 1945, Notes, 3:00 P.M., typescript, 24 p.; Minutes, 3:00 P.M., typescript copy, 2 p. (Box 1)
        - October 16, 1945, Notes, 3:15 P.M., typescript, 23 p.; Minutes, 3:00 P.M., typescript copy revised, 2 p. (Box 1)
        - October 17, 1945, Notes, 10:40 A.M., typescript, 39 p.; Minutes, 10:30 A.M., typescript copy, 2 p.; Minutes, 4:00 P.M., typescript copy, 2 p. (Box 1)
        - October 18, 1945, Notes (first public session) 10:30 A.M., typescript, printed material, 6 p.; Minutes, 10:30 A.M. typescript copy, 1 p. (Box 1)
      - Supporting material
        - Statement by the presiding member of the tribunal at the opening meeting, undated; printed material, 2 p. (Box 1)
        - Letter with attached list of German lawyers submitted by the U. S. members, October 14, 1945; typescript, typescript copy, 2 p., undated (Box 1)
        - List of German lawyers, undated; printed material, 1 p. (Box 1)
        - Motion for certain procedural orders, undated; typescript copy, 8 p. (Box 1)
        - Court orders, undated; printed material, 15 p. (Box 1)
        - Rules of the International Military Tribunal, undated; printed material, 4 p. (Box 1)
        - Statement by the presiding member of the tribunal after receipt of the indictment, undated; printed material, typescript, 15 p. (Box 1)
        - Organizational plan of secretariat, undated; typescript copy, 1 p. (Box 1)
      - Notes and minutes
        - October 19, 1945, Notes, 10:45 A.M., typescript, 9 p.; Minutes, 10:30 A.M., typescript copy revised, 2 p. (Box 1)
        - October 20, 1945, Minutes, 10:30 A.M., typescript copy, 1 p. (Box 1)
        - October 21, 1945, Minutes (Meeting in Mr. Biddle's study) typescript copy, 3 p. (Box 1)
      - Supporting material
        - Memorandum for the American secretary, October 23, 1945; typescript copy, 5 p, (Box 1)
        - Applications submitted by defendants, undated; typescript copy revised, 1 p. (Box 1)
        - Defendant's applications forms, undated; printed material, 2 p. (Box 1)
      - Notes and minutes
        - October 29, 1945, Notes, 10:10 A.M., typescript, 18 p.; Minutes, 10:10 A.M., typescript copy, 2 p.; Notes, 2:30 P.M., typescript, 20 p.; Minutes, 2:30 P.M. typescript copy, 2 p. (Box 1)
        - October 30, 1945, Notes, 10:00 A.M., typescript, 23 p.; Minutes, 10:00 A.M., typescript copy, 2 p.; Notes, 2:10 P.M., typescript, 11 p.; Minutes, 2:15 P.M., typescript copy, 3 p. (Box 1)
        - October 31, 1945, Notes, 10:10 A.M., typescript, 18 p.; Minutes, 10:00 A.M., typescript copy, 3 p.; Notes, 2:15 P.M., typescript, 26 p.; Minutes, 2:00 P.M., typescript copy, 4 p. (Box 1)
        - November 1, 1945, Notes, 10:00 A.M., typescript, 11 p.; Minutes, 10:00 A.M., typescript copy, 2 p. (Box 1)
        - November 6, 1945, Notes, 11:10 A.M., typescript, 17 p.; Minutes, 11:00 A.M., typescript copy, 3 p.; Notes, 2:00 P.M., typescript, 16 p.; Minutes, 2:30 P.M., typescript copy, 3 p. (Box 2)
        - November 8, 1945, Notes, 10:00 A.M., typescript, 14 p.; Minutes, 10:00 A.M., typescript copy, 4 p.; Minutes, 4:00 P.M., typescript, 2 p. (Box 2)
        - November 9, 1945, Notes, 2:15 P.M., typescript, 13 p.; Minutes, 2:15 P.M., typescript copy, 3 p. (Box 2)
        - November 12, 1945, Notes, 10:40 A.M., typescript, 18 p.; Minutes, 10:30 A.M., typescript copy, 3 p. (Box 2)
        - November 13, 1945, Notes, 10:30 A.M., typescript, 12 p.; Minutes, 10:00 A.M., typescript copy, 2 p.; Notes, 4:30 P.M., typescript, 5 p.; Minutes, 4:30 P.M., typescript copy, 16 p.; Notes, 9:00 P.M., typescript, 22 p.; Minutes, 9:00 P.M., typescript copy, 3 p. (Box 2)
        - November 14, 1945, Notes, 2:20 P.M., typescript, 29 p.; Minutes, 2:00 P.M., typescript copy, 3 p. (Box 2)
        - November 15, 1945, Notes, 11:00 A.M., typescript, 15 p.; Minutes, 11:15 A.M., typescript copy, 2 p.; Minutes (executive session) 3:45 P.M., typescript copy, 2 p.; Minutes (administrative session) 5:40 P.M., typescript copy, 1 p. (Box 2)
      - Minutes
        - November 16, 1945, Executive session, 10:30 A.M., typescript copy, 2 p.; Administrative session, 12:40 P.M., typescript copy, 1 p.; Executive session, 2:15 P.M., typescript copy, 3 p. (Box 2)
        - November 17, 1945, Administrative session, 11:00 A.M., typescript copy, 2 p.; Administrative session, 2:00 P.M., typescript copy, 3 p. (Box 2)
        - November 19, 1945, Executive session, 10:00 A.M., typescript copy, 1 p.; Executive session, 4:00 P.M., typescript copy, 4 p. (Box 2)
        - November 21, 1945, Executive session, 4:30 P.M., typescript, 1 p.; 5:15 P.M., typescript copy, 2 p. (Box 2)
        - November 24, 1945, Executive session, 2:30 P.M., typescript copy, 2 p. (Box 2)
        - November 28, 1945, Executive session, 4:30 P.M., typescript copy, 4 p.; 4:30 P.M., typescript, 1 p. (Box 2)
        - December 1, 1945, 2:30 P.M., typescript copy, 2 p. (Box 2)
        - December 2, 1945, 3:00 P.M., typescript copy, 4 p. (Box 2)
        - December 8, 1945, 10:00 A.M., typescript, 2 p. (Box 2)
        - December 15, 1945, 10:00 A.M., typescript copy, 9 p. (Box 2)
        - December 17, 1945, 5:15 P.M., typescript copy, 2 p. (Box 2)
        - December 19, 1945, 5:15 P.M., typescript copy, 3 p. (Box 2)
        - December 20, 1945, 4:15 P.M., typescript copy, 5 p. (Box 2)
        - January 6, 1946, 10:00 A.M., typescript copy, 2 p. (Box 2)
        - January 12, 1946, 10:00 A.M., typescript copy, 3 p. (Box 2)
        - January 14, 1946, 2:00 P.M., typescript copy, 6 p. (Box 2)
        - January 26, 1946, 10:00 P.M.?, typescript copy, 6 p. (Box 2)
        - February 9, 1946, 11:30 P.M.?, typescript copy, 4 p. (Box 2)
        - February 16, 1946, 10:00 A.M., typescript, 2 p. (Box 2)
        - February 18, 1946, 4:00 P.M., typescript, 1 p. (Box 2)
        - February 19, 1946, 5:15 P.M., typescript, 1 p. (Box 2)
        - February 20, 1946, 3:00 P.M., typescript copy, 1 p. (Box 2)
        - February 21, 1946, 5:00 P.M., typescript copy, 1 p. (Box 2)
        - March 4, 1946, 3:30 P.M., typescript, 2 p. (Box 2)
        - March 6, 1946, 4:00 P.M., typescript, 1 p. (Box 2)
        - March 12, 1946, 9:30 A.M., typescript, 1 p.; 4:30 P.M., typescript copy, 2 p. (Box 2)
        - March 22, 1946, 2:00 P.M., typescript copy, 3 p. (Box 2)
        - March 23, 1946, 11:30 A.M., typescript copy, 1 p. (Box 2)
        - March 28, 1946, 2:00 P.M., typescript, 1 p. (Box 2)
        - April 2, 1946, 5:15 P.M., typescript copy, 1 p. (Box 2)
        - April 4, 1946, 5:15 P.M., typescript copy, 1 p. (Box 2)
        - April 6, 1946, 1:30 P.M., typescript copy, 3 p. (Box 2)
        - April 10, 1946, 5:20 P.M., typescript copy, 1 p. (Box 2)
        - April 13, 1946, 11:10 A.M., typescript copy, 1 p. (Box 2)
        - April 15, 1946, 9:30 A.M., typescript copy, 1 p. (Box 2)
        - April 17, 1946, 5:45 P.M., typescript copy, 2 p. (Box 2)
        - April 27, 1946, 10:00 A.M., typescript copy, 2 p. (Box 2)
        - May 4, 1946, 12:45 A.M.?, typescript, 1 p. (Box 2)
        - May 6, 1946, 5:00 P.M., typescript, 1 p. (Box 2)
        - May 11, 1946, 12:30 A.M. ?, typescript, 1 p. (Box 2)
        - May 13, 1946, 4:55 P.M., typescript copy, 2 p. (Box 2)
        - May 22, 1946, 5:20 P.M., typescript copy, 2 p. (Box 2)
        - May 29, 1946, 4:30 P.M., typescript copy, 1 p. (Box 2)
        - May 30, 1946, 5:00 P.M., typescript copy, 3 p. (Box 2)
        - May 31, 1946, 5:25 P.M., typescript, 2 p. (Box 2)
        - June 5, 1946, 5:35 P.M., typescript copy, 1 p. (Box 2)
        - June 7, 1946, 4:30 P.M., typescript, 2 p. (Box 2)
        - June 12, 1946, 5:00 P.M., typescript, 1 p. (Box 2)
        - June 19, 1946, 5:20 P.M., typescript, 3 p. (Box 2)
        - June 24, 1946, 5:25 P.M., typescript copy, 1 p. (Box 2)
        - June 27, 1946, 2:10 P.M., typescript copy, 1 p. (Box 2)
        - July 3, 1946, 5:00 P.M., typescript, 3 p. (Box 2)
        - July 10, 1946, 2:00 P.M., typescript copy, 1 p. (Box 2)
        - July 11, 1946, 4:00 P.M., typescript, 1 p. (Box 2)
        - July 17, 1946, 2:00 P.M., typescript copy, 3 p. (Box 2)
        - July 20, 1946, 10:00 A.M., typescript copy, 1 p. (Box 2)
        - July 24, 1946, 5:20 P.M., typescript, 1 p. (Box 2)
        - August 8, 1946, 2:00 P.M., typescript copy, 1 p. (Box 2)
        - August 14, 1946, 2:00 P.M., typescript, 2 p. (Box 2)
        - August 19, 1946, 2:00 P.M., typescript, 1 p. (Box 2)
        - August 27, 1946, 5:15 P.M., typescript copy, 1 p. (Box 2)
        - August 30, 1946, 11:15 A.M., typescript, 1 p. (Box 2)
    - Documents for the defense
      - Criminal Organization, evidence (The Neave Report), August 15, 1946; printed material, 205 p. (Box 2)
    - Notes of evidence
      - Vol. I, United States and United Kingdom, October 31, 1945-January 16, 1946; typescript, bound, 295 p. (Vol. 2) (Box 3)
      - Vol. II, The French Republic, The Union of Soviet Socialist Republics and Argument on Criminal Organizations, January 17, 1946-March 4, 1946; typescript, bound, 166 p. (Vol. 3) (Box 3)
      - Vol. III, Herman Wilhelm Goring, Rudolph Hess, Joachim von Ribbentrop, Wilhelm Keitel, Ernst Kaltenbrunner, Alfred Rosenberg, March 8, 1946-April 17, 1946; typescript, bound, 285 p. (Vol. 4) (Box 3)
      - Vol. IV, Hans Frank, Wilhelm Frick, Julius Streicher, Hjalmar Schact, Walter Funk, Karl Donitz, Erich Raeder, Baldur von Schirach, April 18, 1946-May 28, 1946; typescript, bound, 280 p. (Vol. 5) (Box 4)
      - Vol. V, Fritz Sauckel, Alfred Jodl, Artur Seyss-Inquart, Franz von Papen, Albert Speer, Constantin von Neurath, Hans Fritzsche, Martin Bormann, May 28, 1946-July 3, 1946; typescript, bound, 288 p. (Vol. 6) (Box 4)
      - Vol. VI, Closing Arguments, Defense Counsel, Prosecution, July 4, 1946-July 30, 1946; typescript, bound, 215 p. (Vol. 7) (Box 4)
      - Vol. VII, Political Leadership, SD, Reich Cabinet, SS, General Staff and High Command, SA, July 30, 1946-August 31, 1946; typescript, bound, 170 p. (Vol. 8) (Box 5)
      - Organizations, typescript, bound, 178 p. (Vol. 9) (Box 5)
      - Defendants, typescript, bound, 379 p. (Vol 10) (Box 5)
      - Summaries of Evidence, typescript, bound, 264 p. (Vol. 11) (Box 6)
    - Trial of The Major War Criminals before the International Military Tribunal; Nuremberg, 14 November 1945 - 1 October 1946; Nuremberg, Germany, International Military Tribunal, 1947; 42 volumes
      - Vol. I, Official Documents, 367 p. (Vol. 12) (Box 6)
      - Vol. II, Proceedings, 14 November 1945 - 30 November 1945; 496 p. (Vol. 13) (Box 6)
      - Vol. III, Proceedings, 1 December 1945 - 14 December 1945; 601 p. (Vol. 14) (Box 6)
      - Vol. IV, Proceedings, 17 December 1945 - 8 January 1946; 572 p. (Vol. 15) (Box 6)
      - Vol. V, Proceedings, 9 January 1946 - 21 January 1946; 573 p. (Vol. 16) (Box 7)
      - Vol. VI, Proceedings, 22 January 1946 - 4 February 1946; 567 p. (Vol. 17) (Box 7)
      - Vol. VII, Proceedings, 5 February 1946 - 19 February 1946; 602 p. (Vol. 18) (Box 7)
      - Vol. VIII, Proceedings, 20 February 1946 - 7 March 1946; 630 p. (Vol. 19) (Box 7)
      - Vol. IX, Proceedings, 8 March 1946 - 23 March 1946; 710 p. (Vol 20) (Box 7)
      - Vol. X, Proceedings, 25 March 1946 - 6 April 1946; 652 p. (Vol. 21) (Box 7)
      - Vol. XI, Proceedings, 8 April 1946 - 17 April 1946; 608 p. (Vol. 22) (Box 8)
      - Vol. XII, Proceedings, 18 April 1946 - 2 May 1946; 631 p. (Vol. 24) (Box 8)
      - Vol. XIII, Proceedings, 3 May 1946 - 15 May 1946; 631 p. (Vol. 24) (Box 8)
      - Vol. XIV, Proceedings, 16 May 1946 - 28 May 1946; 633 p. (Vol. 25) (Box 8)
      - Vol. XV, Proceedings, 29 May 1946 - 10 June 1946; 668 p. (Vol. 27) (Box 8)
      - Vol. XVI, Proceedings, 11 June 1946 - 24 June 1946; 673 p. (Vol. 27) (Box 8)
      - Vol. XVII, Proceedings, 25 June 1946 - 8 July 1946; 661 p. (Vol. 28) (Box 9)
      - Vol. XVIII, Proceedings, 9 July 1946 - 18 July 1946; 510 p. (Vol. 29) (Box 9)
      - Vol. XIX, Proceedings, 19 July 1946 - 29 July 1946; 618 p. (Vol. 30) (Box 9)
      - Vol. XX, Proceedings, 30 July 1946 - 10 August 1946; 646 p. (Vol. 31) (Box 9)
      - Vol. XXI, Proceedings, 12 August 1946 - 26 August 1946; 632 p. (Vol. 32) (Box 9)
      - Vol. XXII, Proceedings, 27 August 1946 - 1 October 1946; 590 p.(Vol. 33) (Box 9)
      - Vol. XXIII, Chronological Index, Subject Index, 732 p. (Vol. 34) (Box 10)
      - Vol. XXIV, Document Index, Name Index and Errata, 780 p. (Vol. 35) (Box 10)
      - Vol. XXV, Documents in Evidence, 001-PS, 607 p. (Vol. 36) (Box 10)